ARIEL A. MARCHAND

PO BOX 2491, Grand Junction, CO 81502 marchand.aa@gmail.com • mobile: 970-819-1003

Objective:

Looking an entry level Web Developer position. I want to join a team where I can do client-approved mock-ups, such as wireframes, visual design comprehensive layouts.. Bringing a keen eye for details, strong ability to implement mock-ups, and understanding of great user experience design. I'm currently enrolled in Denver University Web Development Coding Bootcamp.

Skills and Knowledge

- 10+ years of customer service experience
- Excellent written and verbal communication skills
- Superior customer service and computer skills
- 10+ years of cash handling experience
- 10+ Phone Answering
- Attention to detail
- Ability to multi-task and manage time effectively
- Works well with individuals from diverse backgrounds
- Consistently demonstrates self-motivation and dependability, while maintaining a friendly, professional, positive and enthusiastic attitude.
- Extensive knowledge of Microsoft Office, Property Management FOSSE, FOCUS and other property management programs, Adobe Photoshop, Macromedia Dreamweaver and Fireworks

Work History

Village at Steamboat by Wyndham

Housekeeping Dispatcher (November 2017-July 2019)

- Direct liaison between front desk, maintenance and housekeeping staff
- Respond to all incoming staff and guest requests, directing each request appropriately
- Record, delegate and monitor housekeeping productivity for timely completion
- Frequently communicates with front desk on updated readiness status of units to front desk and management

Housekeeping Inspector (October 2016-December 2017)

- Daily unit inspections, assisting housekeepers with cleaning rooms as needed
- Maintains communication with rooms control and performs other duties as needed

PBX Operator (March 2016-October 2016)

- Handle all resort incoming/outgoing calls in an attentive, courteous and efficient manner
- Be able to provide accurate directions to the hotel, and provide information about the hotel and the surrounding area
- Record and relay all guest requests and verify completion
- Process wake up calls per the guest's request

Guest Services Agent (August 2015- March 2016)

- Answers all phone calls, greet arriving guests, assign rooms, issue keys and ascertain guest payment and billing information
- Answer guest requests and find ways within available means to fulfill guest requests
- Deals with challenging guests and find ways to resolve all issues to the guest's satisfaction

Steamboat Ski and Resort Corp., Steamboat Springs, CO

Ticket Office Call Center/Guest Relations Cashier, (Winter Season 2016-2017)

VIA International, Steamboat Springs, CO

Materials Coordinator (May 2015-June 2015)

Administrative Assistant/Office Administrator (December 2014-May 2015)

Fairfield Inn and Suites by Marriott, Steamboat Springs, CO

Front Desk Manager/Acting Assistant General Manager (August 2013-December 2014)

- Oversee a diverse front desk staff to ensure optimal guest experience and smooth front desk operation
- Attend to guest needs at the front desk
- Extensive knowledge of property layout to guide guests and answer questions
- Follow up with guest regarding satisfaction with guest-related issues

Front Desk Supervisor (April 2013-August 2013)

- Process all guest check-ins by confirming reservations, assigning room, issuing and activating room key
- Process all payment types such as room charges, cash, checks, debit, or credit
- Anticipate sold-out situations and obtain satisfactory alternative accommodations when the property cannot accommodate guests with reservations
- Block rooms in the computer and identify designated requirements and requests, contact appropriate individual or department
- Coordinate with housekeeping to track readiness of rooms for check-in
- Count bank at the beginning and end of shift
- Anticipate and address guests' service needs

Legacy Vacation Club, Steamboat Springs, CO

Front Desk Agent (April 2010- January 2012)

Fairfield Inn by Marriott, Steamboat Springs, CO

Night Auditor (August 2007 - April 2010)

- Assist guests with late check-ins and after audit was run check-ins
- Ran the night audit reports
- Assisted with any after hour guest requests
- Filed paperwork accordingly
- Set up breakfast in the morning
- Process cash, credit and debit cards, make change and process gift certificates/gift cards
- Monitor late night hotel activity: walking halls, responding to noise complaints, checking entry doors to ensure guest security

Active Synergy LLC, Aurora, C

Lead Executive Accountant, (August 2012-November 2012)

Walmart, Steamboat Springs, CO

Sales Associate, (February 2012-August 2012)

Resortquest, Steamboat Springs, CO

Night Auditor (Winter season 2008-2009)

Staples, Steamboat Springs, CO

Copy Center Associate (September 2007 - June 2009)

Young Tracks, Steamboat Springs, CO

Supervisor, Lead Teacher (March 2001-September 2007)

Education

Associate in Arts: Emphasis in Early Childhood Education, Colorado Mountain College, Steamboat Springs, CO (2001-2004)